{
    "subject": "resource/Giovanni_Bondioni",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "lieutenant inWorld War I",
    "human_readable": "Giovanni Bondioni's description is a lieutenant in World War I.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9557729363441467,
            "question": "In which war did Giovanni Bondioni serve as a lieutenant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.897054135799408,
            "question": "What was Giovanni Bondioni's role during World War I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8843726515769958,
            "question": "What kind of position did Giovanni Bondioni have during World War I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8716776371002197,
            "question": "Giovanni Bondioni is described as a lieutenant. What does this imply about his responsibilities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8106871247291565,
            "question": "What was the significance of Giovanni Bondioni's role during World War I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7160019874572754,
            "question": "What rank did Giovanni Bondioni hold in World War I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5983611941337585,
            "question": "Did Giovanni Bondioni serve in any other wars besides World War I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5607321262359619,
            "question": "Was Giovanni Bondioni involved in any military conflicts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4933784604072571,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Giovanni Bondioni's military service?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2891233563423157,
            "question": "Based on the information given, what era was Giovanni Bondioni likely living in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giovanni Bondioni's description is a lieutenant in World War I.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1803_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Giovanni Bondioni's military service?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1803_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Giovanni Bondioni involved in any military conflicts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1803_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Giovanni Bondioni serve in any other wars besides World War I?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1803_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1803_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe context information provides a detailed biography of Giovanni Bondioni, an Italian lieutenant during World War I. The documents mention that he was born in 1894 and joined the Italian Army in 1915 as a soldier. He was later promoted to lieutenant merits and served on the front with the 82 \u00b0 Infantry Regiment \"Torino\". The information also describes his capture by Austro-Hungarians soldiers, deportation to a camp in Bohemia, and eventual death due to unhealthy conditions in prison.\n\nTherefore, the triple \"Giovanni Bondioni's description is a lieutenant in World War I\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Giovanni Bondioni was described as a lieutenant during World War I. Specifically, the text states: \"Giovanni Bondioni marquis of Niardo (September 29, 1894, Niardo \u2013 August 17, 1918, Milovice) was an Italian lieutenant, of the Italian army during the World War I.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}